twuffer.com 2019-02-21

# Twuffer

### **1.** INTRODUCTION AND YOUR CONSENT TO TWUFFER PRIVACY POLICY

Grady Britton and its affiliated entities and organizations (referred to collectively in this Policy as “we” or “Twuffer”) respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our website twuffer.com (“Site”) and/or mobile App (“App”) only in the ways disclosed in this Privacy Policy (“Policy”). This Policy applies solely to activity at and information collected by this Site and App.

By using the Site/App and our services, you agree to our collection, use and processing of certain information under the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Twuffer, this Privacy Policy, and our Agreement with you are governed by the laws of the United States of America.

### **2.** WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This policy describes how we treat information that we collect and receive, including that related to your past use of our Site/App and services as well as information by which you can be identified (‘Personally Identifiable Information’). 

You will be required to submit certain Personally Identifiable Information in order to register for access for any restricted or premium features of the Site/App. This includes when you register to set up an account for our service, or when you request marketing information about our service or the Site/App.

### **3.** USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

We collect information and use it to keep you informed about Twuffer, and to make your visit to our Site/App as useful and informative as possible. We may also use your information for some of the following purposes:

To personalize your Site/App experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product features in which you are most interested, or to which you have subscribed.

To allow us to better service you in responding to your service requests.

To process your transactions and set up your access and account, or assist in resolving any problems with your access and account.

To administer a Site/App feature.

We are committed to safeguarding all Personally Identifiable Information we obtain about Site visitors/App users, whether internal or external. The only Personally Identifiable Information we collect via electronic mail, or our Site/App, (including any Site(s)/App(s) currently being maintained by trusted third-party providers), is (1), that which is voluntarily provided by our visitors, and (2), that which is generally found within the user’s browser, for purposes of identification.

### **4.** TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

a) Personally Identifiable Information   
Personally Identifiable Information includes, without limitation, information such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, IP address, full user name, password, credit card data, or time zone, that is not otherwise publicly available. This information is used for internal business purposes, such as processing customer product or service orders or our own marketing activities, and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes without your consent. 

b) Non-Personal Information   
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. For example, our Site/App may automatically recognize the name, URL/domain name or IP address(es) of a website, mobile App, social media platform, or advertisement, through which you navigated to reach our Site/App, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Site, unless it is expressly provided by the visitor. The information collected is used solely for internal review. 

### **5.** INFORMATION SHARING WITH OTHER PARTIES

Information is collected and analyzed so that we may provide our products or services to you, communicate with you, or improve our service offerings to our users. This information is kept confidential. We may share Personally Identifiable Information about you to other companies or people when one or more of the following conditions apply: 

  * We have your consent to share information;
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; or
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on our behalf to assist us in providing our service to you, such as Site hosting and maintenance, billing, database storage or management, or direct marketing campaigns. Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the Personally Identifiable Information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us, and these parties will only be provided with the information necessary to perform services related to the Site/App, and only pursuant to agreement(s) requiring that they maintain the security and privacy of your information.

In addition, in the event of a transfer of ownership of Twuffer such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any Personally Identifying Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may also release information when we believe it is necessary and appropriate to comply with applicable laws or to protect the rights, property or safety of Twuffer, our employees, customers, Site visitors and App users, or others.

### **6.** COOKIES

This Site employs the use of “cookie” technology. A cookie is a small data file that we place your computer hard drive. We do not use cookies to collect Personally Identifiable Information. Cookies enable us to track usage patterns and deliver customized content and features to users. 

We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to understand how you interact with the Site/App, to monitor aggregate use of our Site/App, web traffic, Site/App routing, and to improve or trouble shoot the Site/App. A session cookie enables some of our Site/App features to work properly, and is deleted from your computer when you leave or disconnect from the Site/App. A persistent cookie will remain on your computer hard drive after you close your internet browser, and may be used on your subsequent visits to our Site. 

You may remove persistent cookies by following your web browser instructions to do so. You may also edit your browser’s options to decline accepting cookies, or to advise you before you accept a cookie from any Site you visit. 

### **7.** TWUFFER PRIVACY POLICY REGARDING CHILDREN

Twuffer does not market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child to divulge personal information. We do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from a child under the age of 13.

The Site/App is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian of a child learns that his or her child has provided us with Personally Identifiable Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at our service help email account (x@twuffer.com). If we become aware that we are in possession of Personally Identifiable Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete the information from our files. 

### **8.** PROTECTION OF USER INFORMATION

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. For example, your Personally Identifiable Information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information or account, we offer the use of a secure server at our Site/App. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

### **9.** USE OF ANALYTICS FOR THE SITE

We use or may in the future use analytics tools (“Analytics”) to collect information about use of the Site/App. 

Analytics collect information such as how often users visit this Site, what features they use when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this Site. We use the information we get from Analytics only to improve the Site/App. Analytic collect the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this Site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Analytics with personally identifiable information. 

### **10.** PROBLEM OR QUESTION RESOLUTION

If problems or questions arise regarding the status of your information, users may contact us by any of the means identified in this Policy. We are committed to responding to and resolving problems or questions within a reasonable time frame.

### **11.** INFORMATION SECURITY

The security and confidentiality of your Personally Identifiable Information is very important to Twuffer. We restrict access to your Personally Identifying Information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Site/App or services. We use administrative, electronic and physical methods as appropriate to protect your information from unauthorized access. 

We will, when legally required, inform our users and subscribers in the event of any breach of the security or confidentiality of your unencrypted and stored Personally Identifiable Information. We will so inform you by direct email and/or by prominently posting such event on our Site/App, without unreasonable delay. 

### **12.** REVIEWING, UPDATING OR REMOVING YOUR INFORMATION; UNSUBSCRIBING

Registered users of the Site/App may access their own personal or contact information and contact us about inaccuracies they may find, or update their information, by contacting us by the means identified in the Policy. 

If you no longer wish to receive communications from Twuffer, you may unsubscribe from them at any time.

### **13.** CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes to the Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy in our Site/App

### **14.** CONTACT INFO.

Twuffer may be contacted by any of the following methods:

**Twitter:** [@twuffer](https://twitter.com/twuffer)

**Email:** [support@twuffer.com](mailto:support@twuffer.com)

**Postal Mail:**   
Twuffer   
c/o Grady Britton   
107 SE Washington St, Ste 300   
Portland OR 97214
